Carlos Humberto Montoya

Personal info

Address: carrera 85 # 38-07, Cali, Colombia

Phone number: 3146271618

Email address: carlosmontoya@outlook.com

Web: https://github.com/carlosmontoya89

Profile

A driven, open minded, creative and successful software developer with a strong sense of dedication and commitment, and over 4 years of progressive experience using object-oriented development. Great capacity for learning and for solving complex problems, and forging strong relationships with business partners

Work Experience

RUEDATA BACKEND DEVELOPER

07/2019 - present

Cali Colombia

Development of a Restful API to control all the information about the customers, vehicles, and

mostly the vehicle tires. Leveraged Knowledge: AWS Elastic Beanstalk, AWS RDS, AWS S3, Flask RESTful, POSTGRESQL,

firebase admin SDK.

TSO MOBILE

Development Engineer

10/2016 - 07/2019

Cali Colombia -Design of a Smartboard with parsers to different sensors using Python, and different communication protocols such as RS232, Bluetooth, RS485, TCP/IP, SMTP, TFTP, HTTP, UDP and

-Integration of GPS units and peripherals connected to them, including Temperature Sensors,

RFID, Fatigue Monitor, Fuel Sensors, Jbox, etc. Design Scripts for genx GPS Units.

-Leveraged knowledge: Flask, Django, SQLAlchemy.

CETOCO SAS

Development Engineer

06/2014 - 01/2016

Cali Colombia

- Development of a smart weather station using a rasperry pi and an intel edison board. - Development of a digital FPV System for a multirotor Drone

-Leveraged knowledge: Sensor Integration, AWS, Programming in Python, Debian, MOTT.

FTP,VNC, SSH among other comunication protocols.

Degrees

Universidad del Valle

Electronics Engineering

08/2006 - 06/2014

Cali Colombia Programing Coursework: algorithms & data Structures, Operating Systems, Networks, EE Coursework: Embedded Systems, IOT, Computer Arch, Circuits, logic Design, Signal

Processing, Artificial Neural Networks

Skills

Programming Languages

Project Management Methods

Python **FLASK DJANGO** SQLAlchemy



Scrum JIRA Slack



Languages

English Spanish

